## Pedrazzoli Daniele

# Electrical engineer App Developer Embedded system programmer

Recent graduate in Electronic Engineering with experience in designing microcontroller-based systems and developing iOS, Android, and desktop applications for interfacing.

Quick learner, motivated to explore new technologies in electronics and computer science

## **Work Experience**

## App developer

Jan 2023 - Feb 2023

Gamma sistemi, Novellara (RE)

Working for occasional work as a developer for an IOS and Android application using the Flutter framework. Communicating with micro controllers using wireless communication such as WiFi

## App developer

Apr 2023 - Sept 2023

Gamma sistemi, Novellara (RE)

Working for occasional work as a developer for an Android application using the Flutter framework that act as a monitor for an external CPU.

#### Intern

Mar 2019 - Apr 2019

Rebix, Novellara (RE)

Stage for the school. Worked as a welder of THT and SMD components on electronic boards

## **Education**

#### Univesità degli studi di Modena e Reggio Emilia

2019 - 2024

Modena - Bachelor degree

Bachelor degree in electrical Engigneering

## ITIS Leonardo da Vinci

2014 - 2019

Carpi (MO) - High school diploma

High school diploma in the field of Electronics branch of automation



## Contact

danielepedrazzoli2000@gmail.com
Campagnola Emilia (RE), Italy
<a href="https://danielepedrazzoli.github.io">https://danielepedrazzoli.github.io</a>

## **Area of interest**

- Electronics adn Embedded
  System design
- Microcontroller programming

## Soft skills

- Curiosity
- Critical thinking
- Analysis
- Attention to details
- Quick learner

## Languages

- Italian (native language)
- English (B2)

## Skills (Electronics and Embedded)

#### Hardware

- Welding experience for both THT and SMD components
- Circuit design for micro controller system
- Experience in usage of board STM32x, ESP32, ESP8266, Arduino based board
- Experience with Schematic Editor software like KiCad and Eagle
- Experience with electronic circuit simulator like LTSpice, MC11 and MC12

#### Network and device communication

- WFi protocol, BLE and classical Bluetooth protocol
- SPI and I2C protocol for device serial communication

#### Robotics

- Acceleration and gyroscope based system using quaternions based algorithm
- FIR and IIR Filter design for handle data from sensor in real time
- PLC programming and usage

## Skills (Software developer)

## Software (frontend)

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript knowledge
- Flutter for building Web application
- Flutter for building Mobile Application

## Software (backend)

- · NodeJS (express) for server side programming
- Flutter framework for desktop and Dart for console application

#### Programming language experience

HTML and CSS	JavaScript	Typescript	C and C++
6 years	7 years	4 years	8 years
Dart (and flutter SDK)	Assembly	Java	Python
5 years	1 year	Beginner level	Beginner level